Guide to the Guerrilla Girls Archive, 1985-2015 MSS.274
Fales Library and Special Collections
Guerrilla Girls Archive
1985-ongoing
Fales Library and Special Collections
Guerrilla Girls (Group of artists)
MSS.274
9 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, 3 oversize boxes, and 1 oversize folder
7 websites in 7 archived websites.
637 Megabytes in 11 files
Founded in 1985, the Guerrilla Girls are a feminist art collective who focus on issues of gender and racial inequity in the art world, specifically the under-representation of women and minorities in museum and gallery exhibitions. Guerrilla Girls BroadBand continues the works of the Guerrilla Girls, with a special focus on web activism. Their archive includes posters, financial and legal documents, correspondence, and printed ephemera that span the existence of the collective and shed light on its transition from upstart activist group to a trio of organizations, each with their own feminist focus.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the repository email.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Arrangement
Primarily, collection materials are arranged chronologically within each series. Undated materials are generally found at the end of each series or subseries. Realia, video, and audio media have been separated out into a separate subseries to facilitate usage. Each object and media element have then been assigned unique identification numbers.
The collection is arranged into eight series:
Series I. Administrative Records Subseries A. Guerrilla Girls Notes, Correspondence, and Clippings
Subseries B. GuerrillaGirlsBroadBand Notes and Correspondence
Subseries C. Financial Documentation and Accounting Records
Subseries D. Archive Sale Documentation and Correspondence
Series II. Legal Records and Related Correspondence Subseries A. Legal Documents and Proceedings
Subseries B. Miscellaneous Legal Correspondence and Research Notes
Series III. Lectures, Performances, and Exhibitions Subseries A. Gig Notes, Correspondence, and Clippings
Subseries B. Related Catalogs and Publications
Series IV. Research and Notes Subseries A. Guerrilla Girls Project Notes
Subseries B. Miscellaneous Research and Clippings
Series V. Posters and Graphic Works Subseries A. Posters
Subseries B. Postcards, Stickers, and Miscellaneous Graphic Works
Subseries C. Dimensional Works and Ephemera
Series VI. Publications Subseries A. Publications
Subseries B. Proofs and Notes
Series VII. Media Subseries A. Originals
Series VIII. Archived Websites
The Oversize Series is preserved in boxes 7 and 8. This series includes materials from Series III, V, and VI.
Historical Note
In 1985, a group of female artists, incensed by an exhibition at the Museum of Modern Art that included 165 artists but only 17 women, founded the Guerrilla Girls. From that point on, using statistics-based, text-centric posters and billboards, the group sought to educate the art world about its own institutionalized discrimination by targeting art institutions and art critics who failed to provide women and minorities representation. The group also staged public interventions while wearing gorilla masks to protect their identities. Anonymity is a key aspect of the group's activism, and members (primarily artists) adopt the names of overlooked artists as pseudonyms.
In the late nineties, the Guerrilla Girls entered a phase during which some of its founding members split apart from the group. Disagreements over focus, financial dealings, and the future of the collective's mission led to the formation of three separate groups, all three of which still functioned as of 2013. Today, the GuerrillaGirlsBroadBand, Inc., Guerrilla Girls On Tour, Inc. (the Theatre Girls), and Guerrilla Girls, Inc. all continue to promote the objectives of the collectives.
Guerrilla Girls BroadBand was formed in 2001. While continuing the aims of the original Guerrilla Girls, it sees the world wide web as its "natural habitat". From their viewpoint, the "original Unincorporated Collective of Guerrilla Girls had come unstuck partly through a lack of agreed procedures for such things as diversity, power-sharing, and collective rights to intellectual property. The Broads set out to fix these problems and blaze a trail for future collective artistic endeavours."
Sources:
Guerrilla Girls BroadBand "about page" (ggbb.org/about) Guerrilla Girls chronology (www.guerrillagirls.com/info/index.shtml)
Provenance
The collection was donated to NYU's Fales Library and Special Collections by artist and Franklin Furnace founder Martha Wilson in 2010. Additional materials were donated in 2015; the accession number associated with this gift is 2015.274.
http://www.guerrillagirls.com/ was initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2007 as part of the Other Left Activism Web Archive. In 2015, these websites were migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2017, crawling was discontinued in the Other Left Activism Web Archive and restarted in the Guerrilla Girls Web Archive. http://guerrillagirlsbroadband.com was initially captured in 2015 in the Guerrilla Girls Web Archive and continued in 2017 in the Guerrilla Girls Broadband Web Archive. In 2019, http://guerrillagirlsontour.com/ was added to the Guerrilla Girls Web Archive. The accession number associated with this seed is 2019.055. Indidivdual videos were added to better capture the videos embedded in http://www.guerrillagirls.com/. The accession number associated with the videos is 2019.061. In August 2021, https://www.themalegraze.com/ was added. The accession number asssociated with this website is 2022.011. In September 2021, https://www.google.com/maps/d/u/0/viewer?mid=1MZdTCzaBYXUxtvr9NqDW5yQbamkwsZhX&ll=53.04642406914769,0.153804424388424&z=7 https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/e/2PACX-1vTMrLOz57uj4FTWDAHDhpfUQpy2grbpcSwfFApuhtJjMGUgy10yhs1VkmZuzOf9xPTZKHR4tvAAKXbk/pubhtml https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WTzPxzXU73Y were added. The accession number associated with these websites is 2022.014. In December 2023, https://www.youtube.com/@GUERRILLAGIRLS/videos/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2024.003.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact NYU Special Collections (special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596) with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Related Collections
Martha Wilson Papers (MSS.175)
Guerrilla Girls Records (2008.M.14), The Getty Research Institute
Scope and Contents
This collection includes posters, financial and legal documents, correspondence, and ephemera that span the existence of the collective from its founding in 1985, to the incarnation and continued existence of the splinter group Guerrilla Girls BroadBand. Records shed light on the group's transition from an upstart activist group, to a trio of organizations, each with their own feminist focus.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedure
An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Art, Modern -- United States -- 20th century.; Art, Modern -- 20th century -- Exhibitions.; Political activists.; Feminism and art.; Political posters.; Women artists -- United States.; Women artists -- Exhibitions.; Art -- Political aspects.; Art museums -- New York (N.Y.); Artists -- Exhibitions; Guerrilla Girls (Group of artists)
- Series I: Administrative Records
  Scope and Content
  Series I consists of correspondence, financial records, invoices, and documentation related to the business dealings of the Guerrilla Girls in all their incarnations. The records include details about logistics of gigs, correspondence pertaining to the "break-up" of the group, and information about the donation of their archival holdings.
  Subseries A. Guerrilla Girls Notes, Correspondence, and Clippings
  Subseries B. GuerrillaGirlsBroadBand Notes and Correspondence
  Subseries C. Financial Documentation and Accounting Records
  Subseries D. Archive Sale Documentation and Correspondence
  - Subseries A: Guerrilla Girls Notes, Correspondence, and Clippings
    - Guerrilla Girls Press Clippings, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Guerrilla Girls Portfolio and Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - GG 1990-1994 [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - GG 1990-1994 [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Mailing Lists and GG Resume, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Resume, Membership Lists, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - GG Mailing List 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - GG 1998, 1999 Retreat [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - GG 1998, 1999 Retreat [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Pre-Break Up Correspondence, 1996+2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - MW Confession and After GG 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - GGBB New Member Intro Packet, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Breakup 2000-2001 Negotiations (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Subseries B: Guerrilla Girls Broad Band Notes and Correspondence
    - GGBB Stationery, Labels and Business Cards, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1st GGBB Meetings 1999, 2000, 01 [1 of 2], 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1st GGBB Meetings, 1999, 2000, 01 [2 of 2], 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 9-21-00 J & E Letter / Marvin Taylor Letter, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - GGBB Misc, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Contains photograph.
    - GG Theater, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - GGBB Constitution, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - GGBB Corporate Papers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - GGBB Press/Launch, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - GGBB Correspondence & Notes, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - GGBB in New York Times 7/23/01, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - GGBB Expenses, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Money for Women/Barbara Deming Memorial Fund, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Old and New Members [1 of 2], 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Old and New Members [2 of 2], 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - GGBB Logo, Constitution, Etc., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Metroland: April 11, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Preview: April 11-17, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Maine Times: April 25-May 1, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - NYSCA 5/22/02, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - September 2002 Intro to GGBB (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - TNYT 10/13/02 Edward Gomez, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - GGBB Press, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - GGBB Correspondence, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Pennies from Heaven Grant, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - GGBB Horoscope, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Lyn Blumenthal Memorial Fund, 2003 (Box 1, Box 40)
    - GGBB Phone Info, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - "Broadband" NYSCA 04, North Star 04, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 20th Anniversary Report Card Project, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - GGBB Member News, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Misc Projects 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Minutes 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - GG Contact Lists, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Broad Blog '06, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - GGBB Resume, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Gunk and Northstar Information and Grant Applications, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - NYSCA FY '06, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - GGBB Minutes, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Lynn Hershman: Women, Art, Revolution, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Louise Bourgeois Film Short w/Amei Wallach, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Second Life/Creative Capital, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Archives of American Art Interview w/GG, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Posters to MW from [_______], 2009 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - CAA Distinguished Feminist Award, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - GGOT & GG.Info site, 2003-2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Subseries C: Financial Documentation and Accounting Records
    - Accounting Info 93-97, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - GG 1099s, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - GG Bookkeeping Runs '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Guerrilla Girls Accounting 97, 98, 99 [1 of 5], 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Guerrilla Girls Accounting 97, 98, 99 [2 of 5], 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Guerrilla Girls Accounting 97, 98, 99 [3 of 5], 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Guerrilla Girls Accounting 97, 98, 99 [4 of 5], 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Guerrilla Girls Accounting 97, 98, 99 [5 of 5], 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - GG Receipts and Taxes '97 [1 of 2], 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - GG Receipts and Taxes '97 [2 of 2], 1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Chemical Bank Cards, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Accounting Info 99 [1 of 4], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Accounting Info 99 [2 of 4], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Accounting Info 99 [3 of 4], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Accounting Info 99 [4 of 4], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - GG Finances (Records), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - GGBB 2001 Bills (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bank Statements/Chase [1 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bank Statements/Chase [2 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bank Statements/Chase [3 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bank Statements/Chase [4 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - GGBB Taxes [1 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - GGBB Taxes [2 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Consultant Invoices, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - GGBB Misc Income, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - To Be Paid/Financials, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - GGBB Reimbursables, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Subseries D: Archive Sale Documentation and Correspondence
    - Guerrilla Girls Poster & Archives Inventory Lists, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Archives and Storage Info, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Archives Commission [1 of 4], 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Archives Commission [2 of 4], 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Archives Commission [3 of 4], 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Archives Commission [4 of 4], 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Archives Sale Correspondence, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Series II: Legal Records and Related Correspondence
  Series II contains official legal documents pertaining to a lawsuit instigated by two original members of the Guerrilla Girls against the other members of the group. Official depositions and motions, along with formal and informal correspondence are included.
  Subseries A. Legal Documents and Proceedings
  Subseries B. Miscellaneous Legal Correspondence and Research Notes
  - Subseries A: Legal Documents and Proceedings
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: 1/16/2001-5/28/2004 [1 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: 1/16/2001-5/28/2004 [2 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: 1/16/2001-5/28/2004 [3 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: 1/16/2001-5/28/2004 [4 of 4], 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Sep. 27, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: July 21, 2003-Aug 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: July 9, 2003-Oct. 16 2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Sept. 17, 2003-Feb. 10, 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Oct. 16, 2003-Dec. 1, 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Oct. 28, 2003-Jan. 24, 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Oct. 29, 2003-Feb. 3, 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Feb. 20, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Mar. 2, 2004-Oct. 13, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Mar. 18, 2004-Oct. 11, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Mar. 23, 2004-Nov. 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: June 2004 [1 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: June 2004 [2 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: June 2004 [3 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Sept. 9, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Sept. 13, 2004-Oct. 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Oct. 13, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Nov. 29, 2004-July 5, 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Dec. 6, 2004-Feb. 14, 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Aug.-Sept. '05 (Some Spring '05), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - GG Legal Decision Documentation: Nov. 5/Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: Miscellaneous Legal Correspondence and Research Notes
    - Negotiation GG/GGBB, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - GGOT Agreement w/GGI, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Search for Legal Representation 10/1/04-2/2/05, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Proskauer Rose 2/2/05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Series III: Lectures, Performances, and Exhibitions
  Series III comprises correspondence related to performances and appearances by members of the Guerrilla Girls in all their incarnations. Postcards, posters, press mentions, official catalogs, and research notes are also included.
  Subseries A. Gig Notes, Correspondence, and Clippings
  Subseries B. Related Catalogs and Publications SEE OVERSIZE SERIES
  - Subseries A: Gig Notes, Correspondence, and Clippings
    - Guerrilla Girls Early Projects MW Did, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - GG @ Atlanta College of Art, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - GG @ Falkirk Cultural Center Promo Materials, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - New Museum Spy Project, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - General Gig Info 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Gotham Comedy Club Event, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - "Girlfriends" Press Notice, November 2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - N. Wisc Press 3/12/2002 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, April 11, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - U. of St. Thomas Gig: Apr. 29, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Anonymous Show/Karen Atkinson Curator, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Art & Outrage: 6/5/2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence re: SVA Panel "Goddesses...Riot Grrls", 2003 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - David Zwirner Gallery "Charley 03" Exhibit, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Funky Fine Fall Line/Curator Judy Collischan/Fashion Week, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Baxten Award: 11/6/03, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Buffalo '04/Network, Art, & Collaboration, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - GGBB @ The '04 Whitney Biennial, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - And So Forth/Jan. 2005 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Art Journal: Spring 2005 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - "Post No Bills" Exhibition/White Columns June 17-July 31, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Santa Fe Art Institute/July 23, '05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - GGI @ Venice Biennale 2005/New Yorker & ArtNews articles (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - GGBB @ Pittsburgh 11/7/2005 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - NYU Gig 3/2/06, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Lynn Hershmann Film 5/13/2006 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - UCLA Gig 3/2/07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Creative Time/Democracy in Action, 2008
      - Paper Materials (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Digital Materials, FA_MSS_274_ER_1
    - Bronx Museum 5/17/08, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Conversation Pieces/Buffalo Exhibition, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Grantmakers in the Arts Gig, 10/21/09, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Series IV: Research and Notes
  Series IV contains correspondence, notes, articles, and clippings used to develop projects including books, performances, and artworks.
  Subseries A. Guerrilla Girls Project Notes
  Subseries B. Miscellaneous Research and Clippings
  - Subseries A: Guerrilla Girl Project Notes
    - GG Project Notes 1996-early 2000 [1 of 4], 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - GG Project Notes 1996-early 2000 [2 of 4], 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - GG Project Notes 1996-early 2000 [3 of 4], 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - GG Project Notes 1996-early 2000 [4 of 4], 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Miscellaneous Project Research and Clippings
    - Gov't Spending Research, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Babes in the Artworld Video Project, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Misc Clippings and Articles, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Feminism Fashion Show, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Research on Work/Job, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - New Work & Research 2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - The Advantages of Another Bush Presidency Notes, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Ideas, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Film and Fashion [1 of 2], 2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Film and Fashion [2 of 2], 2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - GG Research and Clippings 2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Broadblog and Recruitment Research, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Notes for YouTube Videos, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Gertrude Stein Research, 2005-2009 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Series V: Posters and Graphic Works 1985-2010
  Series V includes original artistic output from the Guerrilla Girls including posters, graphic works, and objects.
  Subseries A. Posters is listed under Oversize materials
  Subseries B. Postcards, Stickers, and Miscellaneous Graphic Works
  Subseries C. Dimensional Works and Ephemera
  - Subseries B: Postcards, Stickers, and Miscellaneous Graphic Works
    - GG Pop Quiz 8 1/2 x 11", undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Tragedy Poster 8 1/2 x 11", undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Assorted GG Cards and Stickers, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Photo of GG w/ "Confessions", undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - As Good As It Gets Stickers, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)